//Need an array: objects, first object is a question number, plus question content, all choices, 
const STORE = [
    {
        question: "Which local coffee shop stays open 24/7?",
        answers: ["Halcyon", "Starbucks", "Bennu", "Houndstooth"],
        correctAnswer: "Bennu",
        icon: "",
        alt: "Image displaying storefront of Bennu coffeshop"
    },
    {
        question: "Which bridge can you visit to see the bats?",
        answers: ["Lamar Bridge", "Congress Ave. Bridge", "360 Bridge", "Pennybacker Bridge"],
        correctAnswer: "Congress Ave. Bridge"
        icon: "",
        alt: ""
    },
    {
        question: "What iconic street borders the University of Texas at Austin?",
        answers: ["Guadalupe St.", "51st St.", "Congress Ave.", "Cesar Chavez St."],
        correctAnswer: "Guadalupe St."
        icon: "",
        alt: ""
    }
    {
        question: "What is the tallest building in ATX?",
        answers: ["The Fairmont", "Frost Tower", "The Bowie", "The Austonian"],
        correctAnswer: "The Austonian",
        icon: "",
        alt: "Image displaying storefront of Bennu coffeshop"
    },
    {
        question: "Which local shop is known for selling costumes?",
        answers: ["Party City", "Lucy in Disguise with Diamonds", "Cathedral of Junk", "Austin Art Garage"],
        correctAnswer: "Bennu",
        icon: "",
        alt: "Image displaying storefront of Bennu coffeshop"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following bars is located on West 6th St.?",
        answers: ["Maggie Mae's", "Whisler's", "Shangri-La", "Violet Crown Social Club"],
        correctAnswer: "Maggie Mae's",
        icon: "",
        alt: "Image displaying storefront of Bennu coffeshop"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the mascot of the University of Texas?",
        answers: ["Bears", "Roadrunners", "Raiders", "Longhorns"],
        correctAnswer: "Longhorns",
        icon: "",
        alt: "Image displaying storefront of Bennu coffeshop"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the famous yearly music festival that is usually held in the Fall?",
        answers: ["SXSW", "Austin City Limits (ACL)", "F1", "Waterloo Music Festival"],
        correctAnswer: "Austin City Limits (ACL)",
        icon: "",
        alt: "Image displaying storefront of Bennu coffeshop"
    },
    {
        question: "What river cuts through downtown Austin?",
        answers: ["Rio Grande River", "Guadalupe River", "Colorado River", "San Antonio River"],
        correctAnswer: "Colorado River",
        icon: "",
        alt: "Image displaying storefront of Bennu coffeshop"
    },
    {
        question: "Where can LGBTQ+ and other similarly identified folks go to party downtown?",
        answers: ["West 6th", "The Warehouse District", "Rainey St.", "East 6th"],
        correctAnswer: "The Warehouse District",
        icon: "",
        alt: "Image displaying storefront of Bennu coffeshop"
    }
];